roirocket.com 2018-01-07

# Privacy Policy

**ROIRocket PRIVACY POLICY**

ROIRocket Inc. (“ROIRocket”) has instituted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to exhibit our dedication to the privacy of Advertisers and Affiliates. The following disclosure outlines our Privacy Policy in regards to the information gathering and distribution of data from our web site and how we protect the privacy of our users.

ROIRocket, LLC (“ROIRocket”), a Colorado Limited Liability Company, doing business as ROIRocket.com reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes to the Privacy Policy will immediately be in effect. Except as required by law, changes to this Privacy Policy will not affect your privacy and the privacy of the data that was gathered prior to the new policy taking effect. ROIRocket reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. It is the sole responsibility of Affiliates to frequently review this Privacy Policy as to stay current on any policy changes and/or updates.

**Data Collection**

ROIRocket does not collect any personal data of visitors to ROIRocket, other than those individuals who have a contract as an Affiliate with ROIRocket. ROIRocket is the sole owner of information collected on this web site and any personal data that is transmitted will not be sold, shared, or rented to third parties.

**Affiliate Privacy Policy**

ROIRocket has in place a privacy policy to protect all users and encourages all Affiliates of the ROIRocket network to implement similar policies on their websites.

**Cookies**

Upon your first visit to this web site, a “cookie” is sent to your computer. A cookie is a file that identifies you as a unique user. It stores personal preferences and user data; however, in no way does this tell us who you are. ROIRocket has two primary uses for its cookies.

First, we use cookies to track when banners from our advertisers are uploaded on a web page to be viewed by a user. We also use cookies as a tracking mechanism for our reporting system to approximate the overall reach of ROIRocket’s ad campaigns, as well as rate of recurrence of the display of the advertisements. This allows ROIRocket to determine how often the advertisement is displayed as well as the total reach of the advertising on the Affiliate’s website.

While both of these activities depend on the use of a “cookie,” visitors to this site always have the option of disabling cookies in their web browser. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. Please see your browser supplier’s website for details on how to do this. ROIRocket works closely with Advertisers (“Advertisers”) that offer advertisements for Affiliates to place on their web sites. Advertisers will have their own policies in place with regards to cookies and ROIRocket has no control over what individual Advertisers do with the information that is collected on Affiliates.

**Information Gathering**

ROIRocket collects personal contact information by various methods, specific to information necessary for registration of Affiliates to join the ROIRocket network. The information collected may be used to send the Affiliate company information about ROIRocket or to send newsletters or updates concerning their ROIRocket account. All personally identifiable information that is transmitted to ROIRocket from prospective and approved Affiliates is intended for administrative purposes only, such as tracking sales and commissions to be paid to Affiliates of the ROIRocket network.

**Information Dissemination**

We may use the personal information that you supply to us and we may work with other third party businesses to bring selected opportunities to our members via email. These businesses may include providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation and email marketing.

**Children Under 13**

ROIRocket does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe ROIRocket has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us.

**Security**

ROIRocket has made every effort to maintain the security of all data collected on the ROIRocket website, to protect against loss, misuse and/or alteration of the information that you provide. Furthermore, we have taken every precaution technically possible to prevent any unauthorized access to the contents of the ROIRocket web server.

**Spam**

ROIRocket has a strict Anti-Spam policy in place and does not intentionally send unsolicited emails. Affiliates connected with the ROIRocket network will be monitored closely and are strongly encouraged to implement similar Anti-Spam policies on their websites.

**Opt Out/Modify**

ROIRocket provides every user with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future communications from us, change and modify information previously provided, or remove their information from our databases altogether. You may do

  1. Email: [Click Here](mailto:publishers@roirocketcorp.com)
  2. Website: www.roirocket.com
  3. Postal Mail: 1675 Larimer Street, Suite 640, Denver CO 80202, USA
  4. Facsimile: (303) 534-5021

**Contacting ROIRocket**

If you have any questions about ROIRocket’s Privacy Policy, the practices of the ROIRocket web site, or your dealings with the ROIRocket web site, please contact us via one of the methods outlined above.

This Privacy Policy was last revised on December 16, 2009.
